[
    {
        "question": "Who is Bruce wayne?",
        "optionA": "Superman",
        "optionB": "Batman",
        "optionC": "Iornman",
        "optionD": "Hulk",
        "answer": "Batman"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Batmans assistant?",
        "optionA": "Alfred",
        "optionB": "George",
        "optionC": "bob",
        "optionD": "kai",
        "answer": "Alfred"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the main villian of Batman'?",
        "optionA": "Loki",
        "optionB": "Joker",
        "optionC": "Red hood",
        "optionD": "Scarecrow",
        "answer": "Joker"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Batmans sidekick?",
        "optionA": "Robin",
        "optionB": "Nightwing",
        "optionC": "Arrow",
        "optionD": "Flash",
        "answer": "Robin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Clark Kent'?",
        "optionA": "Green Lantern",
        "optionB": "Wonder woman",
        "optionC": "Superman",
        "optionD": "Aqua man",
        "answer": "Superman"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Batmans Base called?",
        "optionA": "The bunker",
        "optionB": "Arkham asylum",
        "optionC": "Batcave",
        "optionD": "Fortress",
        "answer": "Batcave"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is batmans mom",
        "optionA": "karen",
        "optionB": "Martha Wayne",
        "optionC": "jess",
        "optionD": "emily",
        "answer": "Martha Wayne"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays batman in the Dark Knight trilogy?",
        "optionA": "Christian Bale",
        "optionB": "Natalie Portman",
        "optionC": "Joe rogan",
        "optionD": "Jack Black",
        "answer": "Christian Bale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is batmans son?",
        "optionA": "bob",
        "optionB": "Damien Wayne",
        "optionC": "robert",
        "optionD": "alfred",
        "answer": "Damien Wayne"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the leader of the justice league'?",
        "optionA": "Superman",
        "optionB": "Aquaman",
        "optionC": "Batman",
        "optionD": "Flash",
        "answer": "Batman"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does Batman live?",
        "optionA": "California",
        "optionB": "New york",
        "optionC": "Gotham",
        "optionD": "Miami",
        "answer": "Gotham"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the real name of the superhero Ant-Man?",
        "optionA": "Scott Lang",
        "optionB": "Bruce Banner",
        "optionC": "Hank Pym",
        "optionD": "Clint Barton",
        "answer": "Scott Lang"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is nightwings name?",
        "optionA": "Dick grayson",
        "optionB": "tom",
        "optionC": "Harry",
        "optionD": "Mark",
        "answer": "Dick grayson"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the redhoods real name?",
        "optionA": "Jason Todd",
        "optionB": "Elvis",
        "optionC": "Ryan",
        "optionD": "Tyrone",
        "answer": "Jason todd"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Batman work with in GPD?",
        "optionA": "robert",
        "optionB": "Jim Gordon",
        "optionC": "emily",
        "optionD": "Herbert",
        "answer": "Jim Gordon"
    }
]